Preliminary Guide to the Federation for American Immigration Reform (FAIR) records, 1867-2006 MS2195
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
Federation for American Immigration Reform (FAIR) records
1867-2006
1950-1995
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
Federation for American Immigration Reform
MS2195
225 Linear Feet
Records of the organization Federation for American Immigration Reform (FAIR). The records date from 1867-2006. The bulk dates are 1950 to Circa 1995.
Acquisition Information
Gift of the Federation for American Immigration Reform (FAIR), 1996 and 2007 (Accession 2007.072)
Historical or Biographical Note
Founded in 1979, the Federation for American Immigration Reform (FAIR) describes itself as: "a national nonprofit member organization with the goal of reforming the nation's immigration policies to better serve the national interest." There are also records related to the Immigration Reform Law Institute (IRLI), which describes itself as "America's only public interest law organization working exclusively to protect the legal rights, privileges, and property of U.S. citizens and their communities from injuries and damages caused by unlawful immigration."
The Southern Poverty Law Center designates FAIR as a hate group, and describes IRLI as an entity which is "incorporated under FAIR's tax exemption and still serves as FAIR's legal arm."
Collection Scope and Content
The collection contains materials such as newsletters and other publications, press releases, correspondence, newspaper clippings, legal documents, and legislative histories for the work done by the Federation for Immigration Reform (FAIR). The records date from the 1867-2006 with the bulk of the records falling within 1950- Circa 1995.
Arrangement
Organized into 8 Series: Working records, Oral histories, Publications, Legislation, Court cases, Audio Visual records, Press and publicity, and Subject files.
Conditions Governing Access
This collection is open for research.
Note: Within series 2 there are electronic versions (pdf) of the interviews for Roger Conner and Dan Stein. Please ask for assistance if you would like to access these. The files are currently off-line.
Immigration; Oral history
- Working records, Circa 1965 - Circa 1999; Series 1
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains records related to the administrative workings of the Federation for American Immigation Reform. These records date from circa 1965 through circa 1999.
  Arrangement
  Arranged alphabetically.
  - Accountant invoice, 1985 Deccember 1; Series 1 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - ACLU policy guide, 1976; Series 1 (Box 123, Folder 1)
  - Acquisition mailing report, 1988 July; Series 1 (Box 85, Folder 14)
  - Activity of the 102nd congress, 1990-1991; Series 1 (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Adjustment of Status (1/2), undated; Series 1 (Box 124, Folder 1)
  - Adjustment of Status (2/2), undated; Series 1 (Box 124, Folder 2)
  - Administration: Conner personal (1/2), 1979; Series 1 (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - Administration: Conner personal (2/2), 1979; Series 1 (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - Administration: Conner personal, 1980; Series 1 (Box 58, Folder 2)
  - Administrative Appeal Unit, 1987; Series 1 (Box 123, Folder 3)
  - Administrative Conference, 1989 December 12; Series 1 (Box 131, Folder 4)
  - Administrative Proceedings Representation, 1989; Series 1 (Box 123, Folder 4)
  - Agriculture, 1979-1982; Series 1 (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - Agriculture, 1987; Series 1 (Box 46, Folder 9)
  - Agriculture committee (house), 1983; Series 1 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Agricultural workers, 1979, 1981-1985; Series 1 (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - AIDS testing for immigrants, 1987; Series 1 (Box 123, Folder 5)
  - AILA Seminar on IRCA, 1987 November 13; Series 1 (Box 139, Folder 4)
  - AIS-IRLI booklet, 1987; Series 1 (Box 123, Folder 8)
  - AIS-IRLI booklet, 1987; Series 1 (Box 123, Folder 6)
  - AIS-IRLI booklet, 1987; Series 1 (Box 123, Folder 7)
  - Aliens and Nationality, undated; Series 1 (Box 122, Folder 12)
  - American Bar Association, undated; Series 1 (Box 122, Folder 15)
  - American business for legal immigration, undated; Series 1 (Box 117, Folder 4)
  - American Civic Responsibilities Union, 1987; Series 1 (Box 123, Folder 2)
  - American engineering association, 1983-1990; Series 1 (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - American Express, 1987-1989; Series 1 (Box 123, Folder 11)
  - American friends service committee (1/2), undated; Series 1 (Box 120, Folder 2)
  - American Immigration Lawyers Association, undated; Series 1 (Box 123, Folder 14)
  - American Immigration Lawyers Association, 1990 April 12; Series 1 (Box 123, Folder 12)
  - American Immigration Lawyers Association, undated; Series 1 (Box 123, Folder 13)
  - American immigration lawyers association membership directory and bylaws, 1989; Series 1 (Box 128, Folder 14)
  - American legion, 1986-1989; Series 1 (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - Amnesty, 1982-1985; Series 1 (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - Annual National Legal Conference on Immigration and Refugee Policy, 1988; Series 1 (Box 128, Folder 13)
  - Annual National Legal Conference on Immigration and Refugee policy, 1989; Series 1 (Box 132, Folder 2)
  - Appropriations committee (house), 1983; Series 1 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Appropriations committee (house), 1984; Series 1 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Appropriations committee (senate), 1983; Series 1 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Appropriations committee (senate), 1984; Series 1 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Asian affairs refugee hearings, 1979; Series 1 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Asylum, 1981, 1983, 1985-1987; Series 1 (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Asylum (1/2), 1987-1989; Series 1 (Box 124, Folder 4)
  - Asylum (2/2), 1987-1989; Series 1 (Box 124, Folder 5)
  - Attorney contact guidelines and fees, 1986; Series 1 (Box 124, Folder 18)
  - Attorneys general, 1988-1989; Series 1 (Box 125, Folder 4)
  - AuPair Program letters and history, 1988; Series 1 (Box 64, Folder 5)
  - AYUDA Legalization Manual (1/2), 1989 January 30; Series 1 (Box 119, Folder 7)
  - AYUDA legalization manual (2/2), undated; Series 1 (Box 120, Folder 1)
  - Balch institute for ethnic studies, 1987; Series 1 (Box 134, Folder 10)
  - Bank statements, 1984 May - 1985; Series 1 (Box 37, Folder 36)
  - Bank statements FY1986, 1985 May - 1986 April; Series 1 (Box 37, Folder 37)
  - Barnaby Zall, 1983; Series 1 (Box 46, Folder 16)
  - Barnaby Zall, 1983; Series 1 (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Barnaby Zall, 1983; Series 1 (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - Barnaby Zall, 1983; Series 1 (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - Barnaby Zall, 1983; Series 1 (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - Barnaby Zall, 1983; Series 1 (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Barnaby Zall, 1983; Series 1 (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - Barnaby Zall, 1983; Series 1 (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - Benefits for aliens, 1984-1989; Series 1 (Box 134, Folder 12)
  - Bill implementation correspondence, undated; Series 1 (Box 138, Folder 4)
  - BJ correspondence, 1981-1983; Series 1 (Box 57, Folder 4)
  - BJ lobbying, 1982-1983; Series 1 (Box 57, Folder 1)
  - BJ lobbying, 1982-1983; Series 1 (Box 57, Folder 2)
  - BJ lobbying, 1982-1983; Series 1 (Box 57, Folder 3)
  - BJ media, 1982-1984; Series 1 (Box 57, Folder 5)
  - BJ organizations, 1982-1983; Series 1 (Box 57, Folder 6)
  - BJ publications, 1981-1984; Series 1 (Box 57, Folder 7)
  - Black caucus, 1984; Series 1 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Blacks and immigration, 1979, 1982-1983; Series 1 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Board book, 1985 January; Series 1 (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Board meeting, 1989 May 5; Series 1 (Box 150, Folder 4)
  - Board meeting, 1989 September 8; Series 1 (Box 150, Folder 3)
  - Board Member correspondence (1/3), 1986-1988; Series 1 (Box 152, Folder 4)
  - Board Member correspondence (2/3), 1986-1988; Series 1 (Box 152, Folder 5)
  - Board Member correspondence (3/3), 1986-1988; Series 1 (Box 152, Folder 6)
  - Board Member correspondence (1/3), 1989 July-December; Series 1 (Box 151, Folder 5)
  - Board Member correspondence (2/3), 1989 July-December; Series 1 (Box 151, Folder 6)
  - Board Member correspondence (3/3), 1989 July-December; Series 1 (Box 151, Folder 7)
  - Board of advisors, 1983, 1985; Series 1 (Box 33, Folder 19)
  - Board of directors and fundraising, 1989; Series 1 (Box 128, Folder 8)
  - Board of directors immigration packet, 1989 February 3; Series 1 (Box 150, Folder 1)
  - Board reports - governmental relations department, 1985; Series 1 (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - Board reports - governmental relations department, 1986; Series 1 (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Board reports - governmental relations department, 1987; Series 1 (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Board reports - governmental relations department, 1988; Series 1 (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - Board reports - governmental relations department, 1989; Series 1 (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Board reports - governmental relations department, 1990; Series 1 (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - Board reports - governmental relations department, 1991; Series 1 (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Border crossings, 1965-1985; Series 1 (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - Border enforcement, 1988; Series 1 (Box 134, Folder 15)
  - Border patrol, 1981, 1985-1986; Series 1 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Briefing on HR. 3810, 1986 September 11; Series 1 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Briefing on HR. 6514, 1982 September 21-23; Series 1 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Briefing on immigration, 1985 March 22; Series 1 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Briefing on worker's competition with immigrants, 1985 June 20; Series 1 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Budgets, 1984; Series 1 (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Budget, 1989; Series 1 (Box 85, Folder 15)
  - Budget impacts of immigration, 1986; Series 1 (Box 134, Folder 16)
  - Cable on newly-signed IRCA, 1986 November 6; Series 1 (Box 138, Folder 5)
  - California Ballot Initiative to Reduce Immigration, 1989; Series 1 (Box 124, Folder 3)
  - Call-in social security number verification system, undated; Series 1 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - CAPS Californians for population stabilization, 1989-1990; Series 1 (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - Career services, 1988; Series 1 (Box 134, Folder 17)
  - Casa Marianella, 1989; Series 1 (Box 125, Folder 5)
  - Casa Marianella, 1988; Series 1 (Box 134, Folder 19)
  - Census: APA research/cases, undated; Series 1 (Box 89, Folder 5)
  - Census: constitutional convention research/cases, 1987; Series 1 (Box 89, Folder 6)
  - Census: fundraising, 1989; Series 1 (Box 106, Folder 13)
  - Census: fundraising in congressional visits, undated; Series 1 (Box 106, Folder 12)
  - Census: lawsuits, 1988-1989; Series 1 (Box 86, Folder 9)
  - Census: meeting notes, 1989; Series 1 (Box 105, Folder 10)
  - Census: solicitation to congress, undated; Series 1 (Box 105, Folder 9)
  - Chamber of commerce, 1985; Series 1 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Chamber of commerce, 1989-1990; Series 1 (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - Changing technology, undated; Series 1 (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Chicago religious task force on Central America, 1989-1990; Series 1 (Box 132, Folder 3)
  - Chronological files, 1978-1980; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Chronological files, 1980-1981; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Chronological files, 1981-1982; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Chronological files, 1983; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Chronological files, 1985; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Chronological files, 1983-1986; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Chronological files, 1986; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Chronological files, 1987; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Chronological files, 1988-1990; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Chronological files, 1991; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Chronological files, 1991-1992; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Chronological files, 1993; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Citizens Legal Defense Alliance, 1985 July; Series 1 (Box 135, Folder 1)
  - Citizen's crime commission, 1990; Series 1 (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Coalition file, 1989-1990; Series 1 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Coalition for Constitutional Reapportionment, undated; Series 1 (Box 135, Folder 3)
  - Coalition for Constitutional Reapportionment membership (1/2), undated; Series 1 (Box 103, Folder 7)
  - Coalition for Constitutional Reapportionment membership (2/2), undated; Series 1 (Box 104, Folder 1)
  - Coalition for immigration reform legislation, 1983-1987; Series 1 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Comments on DOA regulations, 1987-1988; Series 1 (Box 92, Folder 4)
  - Comments on proposed IRCA regs, 1987 April 20; Series 1 (Box 138, Folder 16)
  - Comments on proposed regulations, 1987 April 20; Series 1 (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Comments on regulations to implement immigration reform, 1986-1987; Series 1 (Box 40, Folder 13)
  - Commissions and reports on immigration reform, 1986; Series 1 (Box 45, Folder 16)
  - Committee on legal immigration reform, 1990 February 21; Series 1 (Box 61, Folder 13)
  - Communications manual, undated; Series 1 (Box 128, Folder 11)
  - Complete count committees program, letter from Clements to Barabba, 1980 February 13; Series 1 (Box 63, Folder 6)
  - Compliance with IRCA, 1987 June 5; Series 1 (Box 139, Folder 1)
  - Candidates for congress, 1982; Series 1 (Box 20, Folder 25)
  - Conference keynote speaker and attendance sheet, 1988 June 10; Series 1 (Box 64, Folder 3)
  - Conference on elderly, congresswoman's caucus, 1979; Series 1 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Conference panel 1, 1988 June 10; Series 1 (Box 63, Folder 9)
  - Conference panel 2, 1988 June 10; Series 1 (Box 64, Folder 2)
  - Conference panel 3, 1988 June 10; Series 1 (Box 64, Folder 6)
  - Conference panel 4, 1988 June 10; Series 1 (Box 64, Folder 1)
  - Conference panel 6, 1988 June 10; Series 1 (Box 64, Folder 4)
  - Conference part 5, 1988 June 10; Series 1 (Box 65, Folder 4)
  - Conference transcript, 1991 October; Series 1 (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - Conference transcript, 1991 October; Series 1 (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - Conference and seminar memberships, undated; Series 1 (Box 135, Folder 4)
  - Congressional border tour, 1986 January; Series 1 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Congressional briefing on immigration reform, 1984 June 4; Series 1 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Congressional globe, 1866; Series 1 (Box 110, Folder 3)
  - Congressional record, 1986 October 9; Series 1 (Box 138, Folder 9)
  - Congressional record on SR. 1200, 1985 May - 1986 October; Series 1 (Box 62, Folder 14)
  - Congressional register, 1986-1989; Series 1 (Box 110, Folder 4)
  - Congressional task force, 1984 June; Series 1 (Box 37, Folder 35)
  - Congressional testimony, 1984-1985; Series 1 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Consolidation of immigration inspections, 1984 March 22; Series 1 (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - Consular affairs, 1981; Series 1 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Consultants, undated; Series 1 (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - Contacts, 1982; Series 1 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Corporation Definitions, undated; Series 1 (Box 133, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence, 1984-1988; Series 1 (Box 105, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence from board members, 1989-1990; Series 1 (Box 149, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence: general letters (1/2), 1984-1988; Series 1 (Box 104, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence: general letters (2/2), 1984-1988; Series 1 (Box 104, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence: immigration litigation and legislation, 1985-1986; Series 1 (Box 93, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence: Jack Martin (1/9), 1996; Series 5 (Box 115, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence: Jack Martin (2/9), 1996-1997; Series 5 (Box 115, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence: Jack Martin (3/9), 1997; Series 5 (Box 115, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence: Jack Martin (4/9), 1996-1997; Series 5 (Box 116, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence: Jack Martin (5/9), 1996-1997; Series 5 (Box 116, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence: Jack Martin (6/9), 1996-1997; Series 5 (Box 116, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence: Jack Martin (7/9), 1996-1997; Series 5 (Box 116, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence: Jack Martin (8/9), 1996-1997; Series 5 (Box 116, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence: Jack Martin (9/9), 1996-1997; Series 5 (Box 116, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence: nurses, 1988; Series 1 (Box 126, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence to board members, 1990; Series 1 (Box 149, Folder 21)
  - Cost of amnesty, 1982-1983; Series 1 (Box 36, Folder 12)
  - Council of economic advisors, 1986; Series 1 (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - Courts and procedures, federal jurisdiction, 1987-1988; Series 1 (Box 114, Folder 11)
  - CR Citation list, undated; Series 1 (Box 122, Folder 1)
  - Crimes committed by illegal aliens, 1985; Series 1 (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - Curtis, 1983; Series 1 (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Danilov, 1988; Series 1 (Box 136, Folder 2)
  - Dan Stein testimony, 1987-1988; Series 1 (Box 124, Folder 13)
  - David Bradford employee performance evaluation, undated; Series 1 (Box 139, Folder 17)
  - David Rockefeller fund, 1989; Series 1 (Box 106, Folder 16)
  - Decennial census residence rules, 1986 December 15-16; Series 1 (Box 84, Folder 23)
  - Defining person research/cases, undated; Series 1 (Box 89, Folder 8)
  - Delaying and reopening immigration procedures, undated; Series 1 (Box 136, Folder 8)
  - Democratic platform committee report, 1980; Series 1 (Box 20, Folder 27)
  - Deportation, undated; Series 1 (Box 136, Folder 1)
  - Deportation procedure: adjustment of status, undated; Series 1 (Box 86, Folder 15)
  - Deportation procedure: asylum, undated; Series 1 (Box 86, Folder 16)
  - Deportation procedure: cases finding frivolous appeal, undated; Series 1 (Box 86, Folder 19)
  - Deportation procedure: judicial review, undated; Series 1 (Box 86, Folder 20)
  - Deportation procedure: legislative history, undated; Series 1 (Box 86, Folder 13)
  - Deportation procedure: procedures and rules, 1988; Series 1 (Box 86, Folder 12)
  - Deportation procedure: s/l cases following 9th cir., undated; Series 1 (Box 86, Folder 21)
  - Deportation procedure: suspension of deportation, undated; Series 1 (Box 86, Folder 17)
  - Deportation procedure: withhold deportation, undated; Series 1 (Box 86, Folder 18)
  - Denver executive committee meeting, 1988; Series 1 (Box 106, Folder 10)
  - Determination of president, undated; Series 1 (Box 122, Folder 7)
  - Direct mail: general, 1989; Series 1 (Box 86, Folder 5)
  - District of Columbia bar foundation, 1987; Series 1 (Box 134, Folder 11)
  - Directories, 1989; Series 1 (Box 136, Folder 3)
  - Discrimination (1/2), undated; Series 1 (Box 136, Folder 4)
  - Discrimination (2/2), undated; Series 1 (Box 136, Folder 5)
  - District of Columbia cabs, 1984; Series 1 (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Document fraud, 1983; Series 1 (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - Drops to the house and senate, 1985; Series 1 (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - Drops to the house and senate, 1986; Series 1 (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - Drugs, 1987; Series 1 (Box 136, Folder 6)
  - Dual intent, undated; Series 1 (Box 136, Folder 7)
  - Due process/deportation research (1/2), undated; Series 1 (Box 109, Folder 1)
  - Due process/deportation research (2/2), undated; Series 1 (Box 109, Folder 2)
  - Due process/deportation research, undated; Series 1 (Box 119, Folder 2)
  - Due process/deportation research, undated; Series 1 (Box 119, Folder 1)
  - Due process/deportation research: administrative procedure act, undated; Series 1 (Box 118, Folder 8)
  - Due process/deportation research: appeals review process, undated; Series 1 (Box 118, Folder 9)
  - Due process/deportation research: fact-specific cases, undated; Series 1 (Box 118, Folder 11)
  - Due process/deportation research: legislative history, undated; Series 1 (Box 110, Folder 2)
  - Due process/deportation research: precedential cases, undated; Series 1 (Box 118, Folder 10)
  - Due process/deportation research: USC-CFR, undated; Series 1 (Box 118, Folder 7)
  - Editorial board, 1982; Series 1 (Box 37, Folder 24)
  - Eighth Circuit court of appeals, undated; Series 1 (Box 121, Folder 12)
  - Election 1984, Series 1 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Election results and new congress, 1982; Series 1 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Employers, undated; Series 1 (Box 136, Folder 10)
  - Employer sanctions, undated; Series 1 (Box 136, Folder 9)
  - Employer sanctions in the states, undated; Series 1 (Box 139, Folder 11)
  - Energy and commerce committee (house), 1983; Series 1 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Engineers, 1984; Series 1 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Enumeration of americans living abroad research/cases, undated; Series 1 (Box 89, Folder 9)
  - Environmental resources and immigration, unknown; Series 1 (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - Exclusion categories and waivers, undated; Series 1 (Box 136, Folder 13)
  - Executive committee packet (1/2), 1988 December 10; Series 1 (Box 149, Folder 22)
  - Executive committee packet (2/2), 1988 December 10; Series 1 (Box 149, Folder 23)
  - Executive nomination of Garcia to INS, 1980; Series 1 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Expert contacts and fees, undated; Series 1 (Box 105, Folder 11)
  - Extended Voluntary Departure, undated; Series 1 (Box 136, Folder 12)
  - External memos, 1987-1989; Series 1 (Box 105, Folder 6)
  - FAIR central file map, 1998; Series 1 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - FAIR house briefing, 1982 June 21; Series 1 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - FAIR job descriptions, undated; Series 1 (Box 144, Folder 11)
  - FAIR legislative hotline, 1985-1986; Series 1 (Box 34, Folder 29)
  - FAIR open letter to congress, 1982 April 1; Series 1 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - FAIR staff list, 1989 May 1; Series 1 (Box 130, Folder 8)
  - FAIR staff and board lists, 1989; Series 1 (Box 134, Folder 2)
  - FAIR testimony, undated; Series 1 (Box 124, Folder 14)
  - Federal Bar Association immigration seminar (1/2), 1988 May 19-20; Series 1 (Box 130, Folder 9)
  - Federal Bar Association immigration seminar (2/2), 1988 May 19-20; Series 1 (Box 130, Folder 10)
  - Federal election commission, 1983; Series 1 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Federal election commission, 1989 October -December; Series 1 (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - Federal register, 1987 May 1; Series 1 (Box 45, Folder 12)
  - Federal register citationL 52 FR, 1987; Series 1 (Box 122, Folder 9)
  - Federalist papers research/cases, undated; Series 1 (Box 89, Folder 7)
  - Field program, 1987; Series 1 (Box 33, Folder 18)
  - First quarter newsletter revenues, 1989; Series 1 (Box 86, Folder 8)
  - FOIA, undated; Series 1 (Box 122, Folder 11)
  - Ford Foundation immigration related grants, 1989; Series 1 (Box 144, Folder 6)
  - Foreign immigration policies, 1984; Series 1 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Foreign students, 1982-1983; Series 1 (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - Foundation center seminar, 1988 July 21; Series 5 (Box 120, Folder 5)
  - Foundation info, undated; Series 1 (Box 107, Folder 3)
  - Fraud hearing, 1987 April 30; Series 1 (Box 40, Folder 14)
  - Freshman in 99th congress, undated; Series 1 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Fundraising, 1988-1989; Series 1 (Box 106, Folder 8)
  - Fundraising, undated; Series 1 (Box 107, Folder 2)
  - Fundraising foundations, undated; Series 1 (Box 106, Folder 20)
  - Fundraising policy and guidelines, undated; Series 1 (Box 86, Folder 7)
  - G. Lewy, Peace and Revolution, 1988; Series 1 (Box 107, Folder 5)
  - General correspondence (1/3), 1988; Series 1 (Box 137, Folder 4)
  - General correspondence (2/3), 1988; Series 1 (Box 137, Folder 5)
  - General correspondence (3/3), 1988; Series 1 (Box 137, Folder 6)
  - General correspondence (1/2), 1989 January-June; Series 1 (Box 152, Folder 2)
  - General correspondence (2/2), 1989 January-June; Series 1 (Box 152, Folder 3)
  - General correspondence (1/2), 1990; Series 1 (Box 151, Folder 8)
  - General correspondence (2/2), 1990; Series 1 (Box 152, Folder 1)
  - Government files, 1978-1982; Series 1 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Grants, undated; Series 1 (Box 106, Folder 19)
  - Grant proposal writers, undated; Series 1 (Box 106, Folder 21)
  - Gray and Company, 1982-1983; Series 1 (Box 37, Folder 34)
  - Handbook for employers: instructions for completing form I-9, undated; Series 1 (Box 128, Folder 15)
  - Health care, undated; Series 1 (Box 46, Folder 8)
  - Hearing of subcommittee on immigration, refugees, and international law, 1987 May 20; Series 1 (Box 45, Folder 14)